# HEATHER ALLARD







## **EDUCATION**

MEDIA THEORY &
PRODUCTION:
INTERACTIVE MEDIA
DESIGN AND PRODUCTION

Western University & Fanshawe College 2010-2014

4 year collaborative program (3 year bachelor's degree, 2 year diploma)

## SKILLS

Creativity

Visual Design

Animation

Adobe Suite

Research

Organization

Planning

Multitasking

Time Management

Cooking amazing food

Planning awesome trips

# **PROFILE**

My professional background may revolve heavily around graphic design and motion design, but I am much more than that. My education, work experience, and life experience give me a well-rounded perspective and a wide variety of skills to bring to the table. I am very creative and have a natural eye for any type of visual design, yes. But I am also extremely organized and love researching and planning all types of projects. I have worked on marketing for huge brands and can work quickly and effectively under pressure. I am passionate about travel and adventure and would love to incorporate those interests in my career.

## **EXPERIENCE**

## DIGITAL EXTREMES

MULTIMEDIA DESIGNER | 2018 - PRESENT

Creating marketing material for very popular video game Warframe. Responsibilities include creating videos and images for social media, high quality title animation for game trailers, video editing, merch designs, manipulating and compositing imagery and art pieces used in promoting the game.

### CINEPLEX DIGITAL MEDIA

LEAD MOTION ARTIST | 2014 - 2018

Producing and animating creative content for Tim Hortons' in-store digital screens across Canada, the US, the Persian Gulf and the TimsTV Network, as well as reviewing my co-workers' projects for approval. I have also built animated promotional material for A&W, Chick-fil-A, and Citizens Bank.

### LIGHTYEAR MEDIA

MOTION GRAPHIC DESIGNER | 2014

Creating advertisements for the G-Tron in Times Square, New York, as well as creating mockup advertisements to pitch to potential clients. A large portion of the job also focused on photo manipulation.

### **BEFORE THAT?**

I've worked as a Fruiter at Cora Breakfast and Lunch, a Cashier at No Frills, a Steel Packager at DJ Galvanizing, as well as a Crane Operator at DJ Galvanizing.